Building mobile apps used to take
months, but today, thanks to AI, you can
create a mobile app in a matter of
minutes. In this video, I'll show you
how to use AI to build any mobile app
you want. And no, you don't have to be a
programmer. So, the app I'm going to be
using is called Anything. You can use it
to create any type of app you want. So,
go to create anything.com and click on
get started right here. Once you create
the account, you should see this screen
where you can describe what project you
want to build. Now, I've prepared a
pretty long prompt because I want to see
what anything can handle. You can
literally type in a single sentence
describing your app idea. As long as you
clearly describe what you want to build,
that is the main thing. So, I'm going to
copy my prompt, paste it into the input
field, and hit send. And that's
literally it. Anything will create the
front end, connect it to the back end,
and even use its built-in database to
store the data. Plus, it will let us run
the mobile app through the built-in
emulator in the browser. So, you can
actually test it both on the web and on
your phone. Now, let's see what anything
is doing. It fought for 2.4 seconds. It
added CH GBD. So, it delegated the
coding part to the best models which is
GPT5 with high reasoning effort right
now. It created the database. It started
creating some front- end JavaScript
files. And I was doing even more
thinking for the generate tab. So, this
app will have four different sections.
So, it'll be interesting to see if
anything can oneshot this app in a
single prompt. Now, while it's building,
let me show you some crazy examples of
what people have built with anything.
So, George right here built a full
landing page. And the best part is the
UI follows all of the modern design
principles. Here is another example with
a very different color scheme. And the
craziest part is this one was built in
33 seconds. As long as you can speak or
type in English, you have the ability to
create and deploy a working mobile app.
It's not just about the creation part,
right? That's one thing. But with
anything, you can also deploy it and use
it on your phone, which is exactly what
I'm going to show you in this video. And
there we go. Anything has finished
building V1 of the app. So, let's see
whether it was able to oneshot this
pretty complex prompt. Again, this is
like nearly 100 lines of instructions,
but there we go. We have the app. So
this is a learning app where it can
create flashc cards and help you learn
any concept from the comfort of your
phone. So let's see if it works. All
right. So we have the homepage. Then we
have the library. Then we have the
active study session. And then we have
the profile. Wow, this is nice guys. You
have to remember this is from a single
prompt. So let's test it out. What would
you like to study? I'd like to learn and
master Reddis cache. Okay, let's do
difficulty level easy. Generate
flashcards. So now it should be using
the built-in AI capabilities. Okay,
there we go. Let's click on start
studying. Wow, guys, I haven't even
given it the API key. You have to
realize in the past you had to go to
platformopi.com, create an account, set
up API key, do all of this hassle,
right? It's it was definitely possible,
but it took a bunch of things and if
you've never done it, it was
intimidating. Now you don't even have to
provide your API key. Insane. So let's
see what is Reddus primarily used for
inmemory key d store. Boom. Correct.
Nice UI green highlighted with
explanation at the bottom. File system
writing. Incorrect. Okay. RDB snapshots.
Okay. This is beyond my technical scope.
But it doesn't matter because we have
completed the quiz. We can see this
final score, the percentage. Now, if you
think this is impressive, just wait
until you see what's coming because I'll
show you that this is not just a one-off
fluke. Anything has the tendency to
oneshot most of the apps you give it.
And let's put that to the test with the
second app idea. So, boom. Once again,
I'm going to paste it into the input
field and let anything do its job. Now,
with this app, we'll take it a step
further and I'll show you how to test
and debug this on your phone so that you
can actually deploy it and use it with
your friends, with your family just by
sending them a single link and they'll
be able to use it on their phones with a
matter of minutes. And the best part is
you can use this exact method to
complete $1,000 listings on Upwork. So,
this is posted 2 days ago and this
person needs a mobile app for physicians
for $2,000. And to be honest, this app
is not that complicated. But because
most people have no idea how to build
mobile apps, they're willing to pay
thousands of dollars for somebody else
to build them. And that person could be
you. So if you watch this video until
the end, you will have all the skills
necessary to build and deploy any mobile
app you want and to actually start
making real money with this. Now, it
might sound funny, but inside of
anything, you can find nearly
everything. It builds the back end. It
has a built-in database. It can do the
authentication for you. It can connect
payments with Stripe. So, literally all
you need is a Stripe account and you can
connect it. No need to worry with the
API. None of that. Anything does that
for you. It has all of the advanced AI
models. And by the way, you can activate
those by clicking the plus and just
typing in Gemini or Grog or Opus and you
can select whatever model you want to
work on your project or even multiple of
them and they will use the tools and
environment that anything provides to
create your mobile app. Plus, you can
build a web app and a mobile app that
both share the same back end. That way,
it's easier to maintain and scale your
codebase if your app goes viral. Now, I
would say the built-in database is quite
OP because you don't have to learn SQL.
It's all preconfigured for you. And this
is one of the biggest roadblocks when
trying to build full stack web apps or
mobile apps securely storing the data.
Right? In the past, you had to spend
hours learning which database to use,
how to query it, how to structure your
tables. Now you can just outsource that
to anything which you follow all the
best practices so that you can focus on
the core idea and the core vision of
your app. All right. So it seems like
the second app has been finished. We
have a bunch of features clean UI. So as
I promised this app I'll test on my
phone and on the right you have these
instructions on how to actually do that.
So first you need to download the Expo
Go app. So on your phone go to the app
store click on search and type in Expo
Go. Now, as you can see, I already have
it installed, but if you don't, just
click on download and then open it. Once
you have Expo Go on your phone, and by
the way, this works both on iOS and
Android. All you need to do is scan the
QR code on your screen. So, there we go.
Boom. And just like that, it will
redirect you to a website. So, just
click on open in Expo Go. Allow opening
project. And it's loading the app. That
takes usually like 20 30 seconds.
Building JavaScript bundles and
compiling everything. Now, while that's
going, we can actually test it right
here in the web browser. So I could say
skill my startup to 10 mil AR. Boom.
Generate habits. Okay. So we seem to
have a bug. So it's actually good
because I can show you how easy it is to
debug your app with anything. So on the
left, let's switch to discussion mode.
And then I'm going to say when I click
the generate habits button, nothing
happens. Make sure we send the prompt to
the AI model. And that we then return
the answer back to the front end which
should nicely display the seven
different habits. Use your builtin AI
capabilities connection with open AI.
Okay, so let's send it out. Okay, so
this was actually faster than I
expected. Anything fought for 6.2
seconds and found that the front end was
trying to call API endpoints that didn't
yet exist. So it created the missing
endpoints. And let's test it again. So
I'm going to give it the same goal.
scale my AR start up to 10 mil AR and
click on generate habits. Okay, it seems
like the issue isn't fully resolved. So,
I'm going to switch to debug mode which
is in beta. So, it's not still fully
released. So, if you cannot solve
something with discussion or thinking
mode, you can try the new debug mode
which is optimized for solving bugs. So,
I'm going to use my voice to describe
the issue inside of the app. Once I type
in what my goal is and then click on the
generate habits button, it waits for
like one or two seconds, but then it
doesn't display the habits. I think the
issue is with the AI connection. Make
sure to use your built-in OpenAI
connector to send the prompt from the
user to the AI model. Boom. There we go.
And I'm going to add think harder at the
end. The reason for this is because by
default, anything uses cloth for sonet.
And the enthropic models actually listen
to what you say. So if you say think, it
will use more reasoning effort. If you
say think hard, it will use even more.
If you say think harder, it will use a
lot more. And if you say ultra think it
will use the most. So just by adding
these two words at the end you increase
the power of the AI models within the
app. So as you can see in the debug mode
anything uses a lot more resources to
debug the issue to think about it to
analyze different endpoints and to
really make sure that your bug gets
solved. Now while it's fixing the bug
let me tell you about the Stripe
integration in the app. Because if you
want to launch a paid mobile app
anything makes that super easy. So all
you need to do is just select your
country of residence and create a Stripe
account connected to a business entity.
Once you finish building, you can start
accepting payments natively through
anything. So literally you don't have to
touch the Stripe API or the code once.
And this is what I mean when I say that
anything is the easiest way to build
mobile apps. I mean they handle the
database, front end, backend, payments,
authentication, logs, debugging, all of
that for you. It is the easiest way to
build mobile apps in 2025. And that's
why I reached out to Anything and asked
them to partner on this video. And
luckily, they agreed. So, if you want to
try the tool yourself, just go to create
anything.com and give it a shot. It's
literally as simple as you see in this
video. Now, I also found this post and
let me know if you want a full video on
this, but this is kind of insane.
Basically, it uses n10 in the back end
and anything in the front end. And this
app scrapes Google Maps for local
business email leads, right? So, no
matter what brick and mortar business
you have or you just work in a local
area, everyone wants more leads. And
this app does exactly that. It has three
different databases and web scraping and
it's able to find local businesses in
any area of the world and give you a
list of emails to contact those
businesses. And this was built with
anything. Okay, let's see if the error
has been solved. There was a lot of
reasoning effort, a lot of compute going
for the fix. Seems like we have some
sort of a fix. There was invalid
ordering. Okay, interesting. But it's
it's fixed. Wow, nice. So I just needed
to describe it and the debug mode is
very OP. Look how much effort, look how
much thinking power, look how much
compute. There's a test. Anything writes
tests for different endpoints, right? If
you're completely new to building apps,
writing tests can be intimidating, but
anything does that for you. Like I I
know like I sound like a broken clock,
but it's kind of crazy what's possible
in 2025. Anyways, I just needed to
describe the error and we have it right
here. So I typed in lose 5 kg of fat as
the goal and we have seven different
habits right here to track daily. So,
let's see. Drink large glass of water
first thing in the morning to stay
hydrated and kickstart metabolism. And I
can click on it. Boom. One done. One of
seven done. Clean UI. Nice colors. Let's
see. Second one. Engage in 10 to 15
minutes of morning stretching or light
exercise to boost metabolism and mood.
Click second. Boom. Completed. Two out
of seven done. Three of seven. Okay,
let's just click through it to see. Look
at the nice animation of the circle.
Wow, this is clean. And there we go. We
completed all seven. We have one day
streak. 100% this week. We can click to
tomorrow. Nice reload animation, guys.
This is clean. What? Reset goal. And we
can choose a different goal. Let me test
this on my phone for good measure. Boom.
Opening expo. Go. Allow. Opening
project. There we go. And here we are. I
am on my phone on the app, guys.
Literally from idea to mobile app in a
matter of minutes. Crazy. Let's reset
the goal. Reset. Boom. I'm going to say
scale my startup to 10 mil arr. All
right. So, the keyboard is covering the
button, but honestly, all I need to do
is just switch to thinking mode to say
on mobile, the keyboard is covering the
button. Make sure to fix the UI. Boom.
And just like that, we can continue
building our app, keep improving it, and
turn it into something truly great. Now,
there are many reasons why I believe in
mobile apps and why this is a worthy
pursuit for you to do. First of all,
there are 17 year olds that are building
multi-million mobile apps, right? It's
kind of crazy what you can do with a
software. Software scales way faster
than anything else. If you hit it, if
your app goes viral, if it clicks within
a certain market, the sky's is the
limit. Also, the mobile app niche is way
less saturated than the web app.
Everybody is white coding web apps.
Mobile apps are way more untapped. Plus,
the market is actually bigger. More
people have phones than laptops. So, not
only is it less competition, but it's
actually bigger potential reward if you
go into mobile apps. So, it is all of
these reasons why I think building
mobile apps with AI is one of the
biggest opportunities there is. And as I
said, there is no easier way that I know
of than using anything to build your
app. So again, go to create anything.com
and get started. Sure, you can watch me
build apps, but until you do it
yourself, until you type in that first
prompt and you see the app and you test
it on the phone, that's when you feel
the magic of Anything.